{
    "id": "6c4d7a811b4748f3a5980f66cca085ed",
    "title": "Participles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………………. a loud sound, we rushed out of the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Hearing",
                "Heard"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "35e57959e0944924829b0a92484dafb6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy cried, ……………….. that he would be whipped.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "thinking",
                "thought"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bf6fb0c5e7d7406bb71370a994f5d000"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. by the rain, we took shelter under a tree.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Driven",
                "Driving"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6b709829a0f7416ab5b3387efd2dae10"
        },
        {
            "question": "We saw a goods train ………………… with wheat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "loading",
                "loaded"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0a16f600131c4e359a3e5afe149d0334"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. wealth is a curse.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Ill-getting",
                "Ill-gotten"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "41ab052799274b629fdaca0c6389e06d"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… with grief she threw herself on the body.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Stricken",
                "Striking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4a3693c2e62647869b12c85d1b203b67"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… with age the old man tottered along.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Bent",
                "Bending"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1c0b4301957f48ed9e0cbcda4659eed7"
        },
        {
            "question": "A ……………… stone gathers no moss.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rolling",
                "rolled"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8a2c9e1932f2496493f97b6bced89a01"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are fighting a ………………. battle.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "losing",
                "lost"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8708e4c9c9a3446ab0a7944d42772b1b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t cry over ……………….. milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "spilling",
                "spilt"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fcd235be8b3540718f86a666de70baa0"
        }
    ]
}